Massachusetts Campus Compact Records MS128
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Massachusetts Campus Compact Records
1992 -- 2009
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Massachusetts Campus Compact
MS128
15.6 Linear Feet 13 boxes
Arrangement
This collection is organized into three series: Administrative Files; MACC Grant Programs, 1995-2002; Higher Education Consortium Grant Programs 1992-1997.
Custodial History
As of January 2006, there were two accessions: accession 1 coming from the Lincoln-Filene Center at Tufts University (initially listed as UA018) in 2000; accession 2 coming from the MACC office in 2005. Examination of documents showed that files are from one and the same office. Files originating from Lincoln-Filene cover the early years of the organization, until 1998, including earlier MACC grant programs such as the Learn and Serve project. All grants appear to be funded from the federal Corporation for National Service.
Scope and Contents
This collection focuses on programs that select Massachusetts colleges and universities proposed to the Massachusetts Campus Compact (MACC). Significant topics include grant proposals for after-school programs and science, engineering, architecture, mathematics, and computer science (SEAMS) programs. Materials include correspondence and memos; financial records; grant proposals and award letters; meeting minutes, agendas, and notes; reports; clippings; publications; syllabi; and program evaluations and reviews.
Biographical / Historical
MA Campus Compact (MACC), formerly known as Formerly Higher Education Consortium for Community Service Learning, is a state-wide membership organization of college and university presidents committed to promoting community service and service learning as critical components of higher education. MACC goals include advancing the practice of community service and the pedagogy of service learning in institutions of higher education; promote collaboration and partnerships between colleges, universities and their communities through programs which respond to specific local and regional needs; and build public awareness of the value of the reciprocal relationship between educational institutions and communities.
Initial efforts to form a higher education state-wide structure to promote student service began in 1992 through a partnership between the Massachusetts (MA) Department of Education, the MA Youth Service Alliance, and the MA National and Community Service Commission. Funding provided by the federal Corporation for National Service supported first collaborations in the creation of the MA Higher Education Consortium for Community Service Learning. These successful efforts led to the formation of an advisory council to continue the development of a state-wide structure to support and promote community service and service learning in higher education. At a landmark meeting at Tufts University with Senator Edward Kennedy on May 1, 1995, thirty-eight college presidents agreed to a proposal by the advisory council to form a state compact network of MA colleges and universities. Following this meeting, an Executive Committee of college and university presidents was formed and on June 5, 1995 the committee formally affiliated with national Campus Compact creating Massachusetts Campus Compact. In 1996 the MACC offices were established at Tufts University with twenty-three institutions joining as founding members.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list.
Teaching and learning; Service learning -- Massachusetts; Education, Higher -- Massachusetts; Massachusetts Campus Compact
- MACC/Higher Education Consortium, administrative files, 1993 -- 2009; MS128.001; 3.6 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains administrative records for the Higher Education Consortium for Community Service Learning (Higher Education Consortium), later on MACC. Includes activity reports and program evaluations. The first folder contains historical information about the Higher Education Consortium/MACC which were photocopied from various other files in the series.
  Arrangement
  This series are arranged by grant, then chronologically within grant, then alphabetically within each year.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Higher Education Consortium/MACC Background and History, MS128.001.001.00001 (Box MS128 Shared 1)
    This file contains photocopied material on the history of the Higher Education Consortium/MACC, which are located within other files in the collection.
  - Consortium Article, 1995; MS128.001.001.00002 (Box MS128 Shared 1)
  - Consortium Program Activities, Folder 1, 1993 -- 1996; MS128.001.001.00003 (Box MS128 Shared 1)
  - Consortium Program Activities, Folder 2, 1994 -- 1995; MS128.001.001.00004 (Box MS128 Shared 1)
  - Building a Statewide Network Conference, 1994; MS128.001.001.00005 (Box MS128 Shared 1)
  - Consortium Evaluations, 1994 -- 1996; MS128.001.001.00006 (Box MS128 Shared 1)
  - Abt Evaluations, 1994 -- 1997; MS128.001.001.00007 (Box MS128 Shared 1)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Appliction Assistance, 1996; MS128.001.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Award Letter, 1996; MS128.001.002.00002 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Budget, 1996; MS128.001.002.00003 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: RFP, 1996; MS128.001.002.00004 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: RFP, 1996 -- 1997; MS128.001.002.00005 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Year-End Report, 1996 -- 1997; MS128.001.002.00006 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Applications Assistance Sessions Year II, 1997; MS128.001.002.00007 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Evaluations-Brad Rose, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.001.002.00008 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Evaluations Survey, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.001.002.00009 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: General Info, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.001.002.00010 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Grant Monitoring Tool, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.001.002.00011 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Grant Review, 1997; MS128.001.002.00012 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Internal Notice of Award, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.001.002.00013 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Invoice Form, 1997; MS128.001.002.00014 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Letter of Agreement between MACC and MNCSC, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.001.002.00015 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Manadatory Grantee Meeting, 1997; MS128.001.002.00016 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: MA Service Alliance, 1998; MS128.001.002.00017 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: RFP Year II, 1997; MS128.001.002.00018 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Semi-Annual Progress Report, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.001.002.00019 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Semi-Annual Progress Report, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.001.002.00020 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Semi-Annual Report, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.001.002.00021 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Summaries, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.001.002.00022 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Year-End Progress Report Form, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.001.002.00023 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Year-End Report to the Alliance, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.001.002.00024 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Miscellaneous, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.001.002.00025 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Addendum to the Semi-Annual Progress Report, 1998 -- 1999; MS128.001.002.00026 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Application Assistance Sessions, 1998 -- 1999; MS128.001.002.00027 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Budget Info, 1998 -- 1999; MS128.001.002.00028 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Evaluation Report - MA Service Alliance Community-Based Service Learning Initiative, 1998 -- 1999; MS128.001.002.00029 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Grantee Meeting, 1909 -- 1998; MS128.001.002.00030 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Grant Review, 1998 -- 1999; MS128.001.002.00031 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Intent to Applies, 1998 -- 1999; MS128.001.002.00032 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Internal Notice of Award, 1998 -- 1999; MS128.001.002.00033 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Presentation to MA Service Alliance Board, 1999; MS128.001.002.00034 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Report to Mayor of Boston, 1998; MS128.001.002.00035 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Request for Proposals, 1998 -- 1999; MS128.001.002.00036 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Request to the DOE/MSA for Funds, 1998 -- 1999; MS128.001.002.00037 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Sample Letter to Legislators, 1998 -- 1999; MS128.001.002.00038 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Semi-Annual Progress Report, 1998 -- 1999; MS128.001.002.00039 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Snack Mailing, 1998 -- 1999; MS128.001.002.00040 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Staff Review, 1998 -- 1999; MS128.001.002.00041 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Year-End Report, 1998 -- 1999; MS128.001.002.00042 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Year-End Report Form, 1998 -- 1999; MS128.001.002.00043 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Application Assistance Sessions, 1999; MS128.001.002.00044 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Budget Analysis, 1999 -- 2000; MS128.001.002.00045 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Congrats and Regrets Memos to Applicants, 1999 -- 2000; MS128.001.002.00046 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Grantee Summaries, 1999 -- 2000; MS128.001.002.00047 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Mid-Year Financial Report Form, 1999 -- 2000; MS128.001.002.00048 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: NOFA Request, 1999 -- 2000; MS128.001.002.00049 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Peer Review, 1999 -- 2000; MS128.001.002.00050 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Presentation to MSA, 1999 -- 2000; MS128.001.002.00051 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Program Summaries, 1999 -- 2000; MS128.001.002.00052 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Proposal Scoring/Evaluation Guidelines, 1999 -- 2000; MS128.001.002.00053 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Request for Proposals, 1999 -- 2000; MS128.001.002.00054 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Request for Proposals, 1999 -- 2000; MS128.001.002.00055 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Semi-Annual Report Form, 1999 -- 2000; MS128.001.002.00056 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Subgrantee Invoices, 1999 -- 2000; MS128.001.002.00057 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Subgrantee Mid-Year Financial Reports, 1999 -- 2000; MS128.001.002.00058 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Year-End Report Form, 1999 -- 2000; MS128.001.002.00059 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Grantees, 2000 -- 2001; MS128.001.002.00060 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Mandatory Subgrantee Meeting Mailing, 2000 -- 2009; MS128.001.002.00061 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Mid-Year Financial Data, 2000 -- 2001; MS128.001.002.00062 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Mid-Year Subgrantee Program Data, 2000 -- 2001; MS128.001.002.00063 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Peer Review, 2000 -- 2007; MS128.001.002.00064 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Request for Proposals, 2000 -- 2001; MS128.001.002.00065 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Request for Proposals Requests, 2000 -- 2001; MS128.001.002.00066 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Request for Responses, MA Service Alliance, 2000 -- 2001; MS128.001.002.00067 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Snack Information, 2000 -- 2001; MS128.001.002.00068 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Subgrant Provisions and Forms, 2000 -- 2001; MS128.001.002.00069 (Box 2)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Application Assistance and Intent to Apply, 2001 -- 2002; MS128.001.003.00001 (Box 3)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Budget, 2001 -- 2002; MS128.001.003.00002 (Box 3)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Evaluation Workshop, 2002; MS128.001.003.00003 (Box 3)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Forms, 2001 -- 2002; MS128.001.003.00004 (Box 3)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Grantee Meetings, 2001 -- 2002; MS128.001.003.00005 (Box 3)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Grantee Summaries, 2001 -- 2002; MS128.001.003.00006 (Box 3)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Grantwriting Workshop, 2002 -- 2005; MS128.001.003.00007 (Box 3)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Legislative Showcase Day and Advocacy, 2001 -- 2002; MS128.001.003.00008 (Box 3)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Networking Meetings, 2001 -- 2002; MS128.001.003.00009 (Box 3)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Reflection Workshop, 2001 -- 2002; MS128.001.003.00010 (Box 3)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Reports (to Alliance), 2001 -- 2002; MS128.001.003.00011 (Box 3)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Request for Proposals, 2001 -- 2002; MS128.001.003.00012 (Box 3)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Review Process, 2001 -- 2002; MS128.001.003.00013 (Box 3)
  - MACC-After School Grant Program: Subgrant Agreements, 2001 -- 2002; MS128.001.003.00014 (Box 3)
  - MACC-SEAMS Grant Program: Grant Guidelines, 1995 -- 1996; MS128.001.003.00015 (Box 3)
  - MACC-SEAMS Grant Program: MACC's Award Letter, 1995 -- 1996; MS128.001.003.00016 (Box 3)
  - MACC-SEAMS Grant Program: Reports to National Campus Compact, Year I, 1995 -- 1996; MS128.001.003.00017 (Box 3)
  - MACC-SEAMS Grant Program: Award Letter, Year II, 1996 -- 1997; MS128.001.003.00018 (Box 3)
  - MACC-SEAMS Grant Program: Grant Information, Year II, 1996 -- 1997; MS128.001.003.00019 (Box 3)
  - MACC-SEAMS Grant Program: Request for Proposals, 1996 -- 1997; MS128.001.003.00020 (Box 3)
  - MACC-SEAMS Grant Program: Training, 1996 -- 1997; MS128.001.003.00021 (Box 3)
  - MACC-SEAMS Grant Program: Year-End Report, Year II, 1996 -- 1997; MS128.001.003.00022 (Box 3)
  - MACC-SEAMS Grant Program: Grant Information, Year III, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.001.003.00023 (Box 3)
  - MACC-SEAMS Grant Program: Request for Proposals, Year III, 1997 -- 1998; MS128.001.003.00024 (Box 3)
- Massachusetts Campus Compact Grants: IN and After School Grant Program, SEAMS, 1995 -- 2002; MS128.002; 8.4 Linear Feet
  This series includes various grant programs arranged alphabetically by grant, then chronologically within a grant, then alphabetically within a year. (1) After-School Grant Program: grant applications and funding records from individual universities. The after-school grant program was intended to support community service and service learning programs that engage college and university students in providing service to school-age youth in the after-school hours, and to foster the development of strong, sustainable campus/community partnerships. Funds for this grant program are allocated to MACC through its partnership with the MA National Community Service Commission. (2) Grants for science, engineering, architecture, mathematics, and computer science (SEAMS).
  This series is arranged alphabetically by grant, then chronologically within a grant, then alphabetically within a year.
  - After School Grant Program - Amherst College, 1998 -- 1999; MS128.002.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - After School Grant Program Proposals Not Accepted - Berkshire Community College, 1998 -- 1999; MS128.002.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - After School Grant Program - Boston College, 1998 -- 1999; MS128.002.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - After School Grant Program - Bridgewater State College, 1998 -- 1999; MS128.002.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - After School Grant Program - Cape Cod Community College, 1998 -- 1999; MS128.002.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - After School Grant Program - Colleges of Worcester Consortium, 1998 -- 1999; MS128.002.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - After School Grant Program - Colleges of Worcester Consortium Year End Report, 1998 -- 1999; MS128.002.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - After School Grant Program - Dean College, 1998 -- 1999; MS128.002.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - After School Grant Program Proposals Not Accepted - Elms College, 1998 -- 1999; MS128.002.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - After School Grant Program - Fitchburg State College, 1998 -- 1999; MS128.002.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - After School Grant Program - Hampshire College, 1998 -- 1999; MS128.002.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - After School Grant Program - Harvard University, 1998 -- 1999; MS128.002.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - After School Grant Program - Holyoke Community College, 1998 -- 1999; MS128.002.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - After School Grant Program - Lasell College, 1998 -- 1999; MS128.002.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - After School Grant Program - Massachusetts College of Liberal Arts, 1998 -- 1999; MS128.002.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - After School Grant Program - Massachusetts College of Art, 1998 -- 1999; MS128.002.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - After School Grant Program - Mount Holyoke College, 1998 -- 1999; MS128.002.001.00017 (Box 1)
  - After School Grant Program - Mount Ida College, 1998 -- 1999; MS128.002.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - After School Grant Program Proposals Not Accepted - Mt. Wachusett Community College, 1998 -- 1999; MS128.002.001.00019 (Box 1)
  - After School Grant Program - Northeastern University, 1998 -- 1999; MS128.002.001.00020 (Box 1)
  - After School Grant Program - Northeastern University Year End Report, 1998 -- 1999; MS128.002.001.00021 (Box 1)
  - After School Grant Program - Pine Manor College, 1998 -- 1999; MS128.002.001.00022 (Box 1)
  - After School Grant Program - Quinsigamond Community College, 1998 -- 1999; MS128.002.001.00023 (Box 1)
  - After School Grant Program - Salem State College, 1998 -- 1999; MS128.002.001.00024 (Box 1)
  - After School Grant Program - Simmons College, 1998 -- 1999; MS128.002.001.00025 (Box 1)
  - After School Grant Program - Smith College, 1998 -- 1999; MS128.002.001.00026 (Box 1)
  - After School Grant Program - Stonehill College, 1998 -- 1999; MS128.002.001.00027 (Box 1)
  - After School Grant Program - Suffolk University, 1998 -- 1999; MS128.002.001.00028 (Box 1)
  - After School Grant Program - Tufts University, 1998 -- 1999; MS128.002.001.00029 (Box 1)
  - After School Grant Program - Tufts University Veterinary School, 1998 -- 1999; MS128.002.001.00030 (Box 1)
  - After School Grant Program - UMASS Amherst, 1998 -- 1999; MS128.002.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - After School Grant Program - UMASS Boston, 1998 -- 1999; MS128.002.002.00002 (Box 2)
  - After School Grant Program - Programs not accepted UMASS Boston Trotter Institute., 1998 -- 1999; MS128.002.002.00003 (Box 2)
  - After School Grant Program - Programs not accepted UMASS Dartmouth, 1998 -- 1999; MS128.002.002.00004 (Box 2)
  - After School Grant Program - Wheaton College, 1998 -- 1999; MS128.002.002.00005 (Box 2)
  - After School Grant Program - Wheelock College, 1998 -- 1999; MS128.002.002.00006 (Box 2)
  - After School Grant Program - Amherst College, 1999 -- 2000; MS128.002.002.00007 (Box 2)
  - After School Grant Program Proposal- Berkshire Community College, 1999 -- 2000; MS128.002.002.00008 (Box 2)
  - After School Grant Program Proposal- Boston College, 1999 -- 2000; MS128.002.002.00009 (Box 2)
  - After School Grant Program Proposal- Boston higher Education Partnership, 1999 -- 2000; MS128.002.002.00010 (Box 2)
  - After School Grant Program Proposal- Boston University, 1999 -- 2000; MS128.002.002.00011 (Box 2)
  - After School Grant Program Proposal- Bridgewater State College., 1999 -- 2000; MS128.002.002.00012 (Box 2)
  - After School Grant Program Proposal- Cape Cod Community College., 1999 -- 2000; MS128.002.002.00013 (Box 2)
  - After School Grant Program Proposal- Colleges of Worcester Consortium., 1999 -- 2000; MS128.002.002.00014 (Box 2)
  - After School Grant Program Proposal- Dean College, 1999 -- 2000; MS128.002.002.00015 (Box 2)
  - After School Grant Program Proposal- Fitchburg State College, 1999 -- 2000; MS128.002.002.00016 (Box 2)
  - After School Grant Program Proposal- Gordon College, 1999 -- 2000; MS128.002.002.00017 (Box 2)
  - After School Grant Program Proposal- Hampshire College, 1999 -- 2000; MS128.002.002.00018 (Box 2)
  - After School Grant Program Proposal- Harvard College - Graduate School of Education, 1999 -- 2000; MS128.002.002.00019 (Box 2)
  - After School Grant Program Proposal- Harvard College - PBH, 1999 -- 2000; MS128.002.002.00020 (Box 2)
  - After School Program Proposal - Lesley College, 1999 -- 2001; MS128.002.003.00001 (Box 3)
  - After School Program Proposal - Mass Bay Community College, 1999 -- 2001; MS128.002.003.00002 (Box 3)
  - After School Program Proposal - MA College of Art, 1999 -- 2001; MS128.002.003.00003 (Box 3)
  - After School Program Proposal - Massasoit Community College, 1999 -- 2001; MS128.002.003.00004 (Box 3)
  - After School Program Proposal - Northeastern University, 1999 -- 2001; MS128.002.003.00005 (Box 3)
  - After School Program Proposal - Quinsigamond Community College, 1999 -- 2001; MS128.002.003.00006 (Box 3)
  - After School Program Proposal - Regis College, 1999 -- 2001; MS128.002.003.00007 (Box 3)
  - After School Program Proposal - Salem State College, 1999 -- 2001; MS128.002.003.00008 (Box 3)
  - After School Program Proposal - Simmons College, 1999 -- 2001; MS128.002.003.00009 (Box 3)
  - After School Program - Smith College, 1999 -- 2001; MS128.002.003.00010 (Box 3)
  - After School Program Proposal - Stonehill College, 1999 -- 2001; MS128.002.003.00011 (Box 3)
  - After School Program Proposal - Suffolk University, 1999 -- 2001; MS128.002.003.00012 (Box 3)
  - After School Program Proposal - Tufts University, 1999 -- 2001; MS128.002.003.00013 (Box 3)
  - After School Program Proposal - Tufts University - Vet School, 1999 -- 2001; MS128.002.003.00014 (Box 3)
  - After School Program Proposal - UMASS Boston, 1999 -- 2001; MS128.002.003.00015 (Box 3)
  - After School Program Proposal - UMASS Dartmouth, 1999 -- 2001; MS128.002.003.00016 (Box 3)
  - After School Program Proposal - Wheelock College, 1999 -- 2001; MS128.002.003.00017 (Box 3)
  - After School Grant Program - Amherst College NOT AWARDED, 1999 -- 2001; MS128.002.003.00018 (Box 3)
  - After School Grant Program - Assumption College, 1999 -- 2001; MS128.002.003.00019 (Box 3)
  - After School Grant Program - Bentley College NOT AWARDED, 1999 -- 2001; MS128.002.003.00020 (Box 3)
  - After School Grant Program - Berkshire Community College, 1999 -- 2001; MS128.002.003.00021 (Box 3)
  - After School Grant Program - Boston College, 1999 -- 2001; MS128.002.003.00022 (Box 3)
  - After School Grant Program - Boston University, 1999 -- 2001; MS128.002.003.00023 (Box 3)
  - After School Grant Program - Bridgewater State College, 1999 -- 2001; MS128.002.003.00024 (Box 3)
  - After School Grant Program - Cape Cod Community College, 1999 -- 2001; MS128.002.003.00025 (Box 3)
  - After School Grant Program - Fitchburg State College NOT AWARDED, 1999 -- 2001; MS128.002.003.00026 (Box 3)
  - After School Grant Program - Gordon College, 1999 -- 2001; MS128.002.003.00027 (Box 3)
  - After School Grant Program - Hampshire College NOT AWARDED, 2000 -- 2002; MS128.002.004.00001 (Box 4)
  - After School Grant Program - Harvard University, 2000 -- 2002; MS128.002.004.00002 (Box 4)
  - After School Grant Program - Holyoke Community College, 2000 -- 2002; MS128.002.004.00003 (Box 4)
  - After School Grant Program - Lesley College, 2000 -- 2002; MS128.002.004.00004 (Box 4)
  - After School Grant Program - Massachusetts College of Art, 2000 -- 2002; MS128.002.004.00005 (Box 4)